<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Jinos Blog</title>
    <link>https://www.jinojose.in/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Jinos Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018, Jino Jose</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.jinojose.in/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Kernel is fun</title>
      <link>https://www.jinojose.in/post/kernel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jinojose.in/post/kernel/</guid>
      <description>Bonsoir!
I was going through some of my kernel docs today and suddenly gotta mood to write on the same. If I speak in simple language, what is kernel? It is nothing but a set of code which knows how to communicate with hardwares. Linux is mostly written in C with a bit of assembly language. Actually this kernel code understands how to interpret your keypresses when you press a key and/or how to communicate with your hard drive to write bytes to it and much more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What a DevOps Engineer Does?</title>
      <link>https://www.jinojose.in/post/devops/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jinojose.in/post/devops/</guid>
      <description>Eye opened for a new day again? Well, wish you all a good day.
Most DevOps professional once was a systems administrator. Definitely, not neccessary. I have seen guys jumping from developer field to DevOps.
I started my career as a systems administrator in NELUX TECHNOLOGIES and after 6 months I jumped to the post of &amp;ldquo;build and release engineer&amp;rdquo;. In AMITI SOFTWARE TECHNOLOGIES I now work as a DevOps support engineer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Systems Engineer/ Devops Interview</title>
      <link>https://www.jinojose.in/post/systems_engineer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jinojose.in/post/systems_engineer/</guid>
      <description>Greetings! corona time.. Huh!? what to do? just job or gaming in mobile? Nope&amp;hellip;After the start of corona first 2 month I took a course from stephane maarek in udemy and by the last of second month I almost completed the course. I loved the course. After completing I was thinking what to do next and decided to take interviews to make use of this year. By the way ..What you did?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Hugo worked for me??</title>
      <link>https://www.jinojose.in/post/why-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jinojose.in/post/why-hugo/</guid>
      <description>Since my BTech course completion I was thinking to make a blog site. I stepped out from college in 2018. Now its 2020. You now know how much late am I.
I will try my best to write my blogs in simple english.I mean, Anyway I know only simple english.
2020 the pandemic year&amp;hellip;which made whole world to sit and spend time with family&amp;hellip;Looking from one side its good but it has its disadvantages too&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
