<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Jinos Blog</title>
    <link>https://jinojose.in/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Jinos Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018, Jino Jose</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jinojose.in/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>On-demand Self Hosted Github Runner Design</title>
      <link>https://jinojose.in/post/github_runner/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jinojose.in/post/github_runner/</guid>
      <description>Whoo hoo! Thanks for visiting again. 🎉
Lets design an on-demand github hosted runner this time. You know.. nowadays CI/CD are shifting to GHA from jenkins. Yeah I know GHA is still not matured enough to tackle jenkins. But it has a speacial advantage over jenkins. AUTOMATION. Automation becomes smoother with GHA. The topic..
Self Hosted Runners.
In my organisation we still don&amp;rsquo;t have an on-demand github self hosted runner. I think most of the companies are running self hosted runners in k8s to avoid expense and to get high performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tried Testkube Today</title>
      <link>https://jinojose.in/post/testkube/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jinojose.in/post/testkube/</guid>
      <description>Hope you all are having a good day.
I tried an very interesting testing tool today. Testkube. what should I call it? 😄 Hmm&amp;hellip; A testing orcherstrator which runs in k8s. Yes thats what it is. A centralised place where all your exisiting testing tool meets.
Bringing all testing tools to one place brings more visibilty and All the test runs on k8s so no usual CI/CD dependencies. What I loved was the setup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Kernel is fun</title>
      <link>https://jinojose.in/post/kernel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jinojose.in/post/kernel/</guid>
      <description>Bonsoir!
I was going through some of my kernel docs today and suddenly gotta mood to write on the same. If I speak in simple language, what is kernel? It is nothing but a set of code which knows how to communicate with hardwares. Linux is mostly written in C with a bit of assembly language. Actually this kernel code understands how to interpret your keypresses when you press a key and/or how to communicate with your hard drive to write bytes to it and much more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What a DevOps Engineer Does?</title>
      <link>https://jinojose.in/post/devops/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jinojose.in/post/devops/</guid>
      <description>Eye opened for a new day again? Well, wish you all a good day.
Most DevOps professional once was a systems administrator. Definitely, not neccessary. I have seen guys jumping from developer field to DevOps.
I started my career as a systems administrator in NELUX TECHNOLOGIES and after 6 months I jumped to the post of &amp;ldquo;build and release engineer&amp;rdquo;. In AMITI SOFTWARE TECHNOLOGIES I now work as a DevOps support engineer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Systems Engineer/ Devops Interview</title>
      <link>https://jinojose.in/post/systems_engineer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jinojose.in/post/systems_engineer/</guid>
      <description>Greetings! corona time.. Huh!? what to do? just job or gaming in mobile? Nope&amp;hellip;After the start of corona first 2 month I took a course from stephane maarek in udemy and by the last of second month I almost completed the course. I loved the course. After completing I was thinking what to do next and decided to take interviews to make use of this year. By the way ..What you did?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Hugo worked for me??</title>
      <link>https://jinojose.in/post/why-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jinojose.in/post/why-hugo/</guid>
      <description>Since my BTech course completion I was thinking to make a blog site. 2018 - College life ends, Blog life starts 🤪.
Good Fun years are all done.. Its time to walk towards my dream.
Oh! I am moving away from my title. So lets talk about HUGO.
I searched a lot for blog creation and was disappointed until I found HUGO.
Mostly I uses duckduckgo and ecosia as my searchengines.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
